

## Personal info

+962785584039
Sarah.abed.elrazeq@gmail.com
Amman, Jordan
Linked in
Portfolio
github
Codeforces
Hackerrank

## **Programming Languages**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

## Skills

Frameworks/ Libraries: React js, Next js, Bootstrap, SASS

Tools: Redux, SEO, Git, Github

#### Personal:

Problem Solving, Graphic design and drawing, Marketing, Teamwork Skills, UX, UI design,

# Languages

Arabic & English

# Sarah Abed El Razeq

# Software Engineer

## OverFlow

I am a self-motivated Software Engineer specialized in Front-End Development with a demonstrated experience in JavaScript and website Interface development.

A problem solver with a zest for solving complex problems. Unstoppable to learn new technologies and integrate them.

# Experience

### Merwas, Queen Rania st. — Front-End Engineer

Feb 2022 - present

- Shipped quality code aggressively to ensure projects are finished on time with minimal bugs
- Frameworks/ Libraries: React Js Bootstrap Redux Next Js

# Digital Framework, Ashmaysani — Full-stack Engineer

October 2021 - January 2022

# <u>Future Auric For Business Solutions</u>, Al Jandawil — Front-End

Engineer

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 · 3 mos

Own business, Online/social media — Handmade, seller, manager September 2018 - March 2020

## Education

#### **Bachelor Degree in Computer sciences**

2021

Al-al Bayt University

#### **Awards**

#### **AFRICA & ARAB Collegiate Programming Championship**

December 2020

Twelfth Place